### Search

Search titles only

By: 

Search [Advanced search…](https://www.autismforums.com/search/)

Menu

* * *

* * *

Install the app

Install

* **Welcome to Autism Forums, a friendly forum to discuss Aspergers Syndrome, Autism, High Functioning Autism and related conditions.**
    
    **Your voice is missing!** You will need to **[register](https://www.autismforums.com/register/)** to get access to the following site features:
    
    * Reply to discussions and create your own threads.
    * Our modern chat room. No add-ons or extensions required, just login and start chatting!
    * Private Member only forums for more serious discussions that you may wish to not have guests or search engines access to.
    * Your very own blog. Write about anything you like on your own individual blog.
    
    We hope to see you as a part of our community soon! Please also check us out @ [https://www.twitter.com/aspiescentral](https://www.twitter.com/aspiescentral)

JavaScript is disabled. For a better experience, please enable JavaScript in your browser before proceeding.

You are using an out of date browser. It may not display this or other websites correctly.  
You should upgrade or use an [alternative browser](https://www.google.com/chrome/).

Privacy policy
==============

Help pages

Help
----

We are Asperger's & Autism Forum ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information please [contact us](https://www.autismforums.com/misc/contact).

What information we hold about you
----------------------------------

The type of data that we collect and process includes:

* Your name or username.
* Your email address.
* Your date of birth.
* Your IP address.

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

* You register as a member on this site.
* You fill out our contact form.
* You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
* You fill out fields on your profile.

How your personal information is used
-------------------------------------

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

* For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
* We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
* Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

Other ways we may use your personal information.
------------------------------------------------

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails in your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

Keeping your data secure
------------------------

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

Cookie policy
-------------

Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on [this page](https://www.autismforums.com/help/cookies).

Acceptance of this policy
-------------------------

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

Advertising
-----------

This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia (“CafeMedia”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here: [www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy](https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy).

Changes to this policy
----------------------

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.

CAPTCHA privacy policy
----------------------

This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [terms of service](https://policies.google.com/terms) apply.
